{
    "id": "a4548c7101a2438fb622feda33acfadf",
    "title": "Kinds of Nouns: Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e2404603384e47d3a3070ef34cec9480",
            "title": "Kinds Of Nouns",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Always speak the truth. Truth is a/an ..................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "proper noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Honesty is the best policy. Honesty is a/an ...................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "collective noun",
                        "common noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "King Solomon was famous for his wisdom. Solomon is a/an ..........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "proper noun",
                        "common noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A committee of five was appointed. Committee is a/an ......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "collective noun",
                        "proper noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We saw a fleet of ships in the harbour. Fleet is a/an ...........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "collective noun",
                        "proper noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He gave me a bunch of grapes. Bunch is a/an .....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "collective noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "London is on the river Thames. Thames is a/an ........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "proper noun",
                        "common noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Cleanliness is next to godliness. Cleanliness is a/an ......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "proper noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Wisdom is better than riches. Wisdom is a/an ...........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "collective noun",
                        "common noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Winston Churchill was one of the greatest Prime Ministers of England. Prime ministers is a/an .......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "common noun",
                        "proper noun",
                        "abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}